Guide to the Nadine P. Winter Council of the District of Columbia papers, Circa 1976-1990 MS2188
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Political correspondence with or concerning institutions and issues, 1976-1990; Series 4
  - Institutions, 1976-1990; Series 4 Subseries 1
    - Washington Afro-American Historical Society, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Washington Area Council on Alcoholism & Drug Abuse, Inc., 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Washington Building Industry Association, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Washington Child Development Council, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Washington Communications Inc., 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Washington Community Fellowship Church, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Washington Correctional Foundation, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Washington, D.C. Apartment Improvement Program, Inc., Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Washington D.C. Association of Relators, Inc., 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Washington DC Keep it Beautiful Student Recognition, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Washington D.C. Othalmological Society, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Washington D.C. Pharmaceutical Association, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Washington D.C. Youth Advocate Program, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Washington Free Clinic, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Washington Healthcare Corporation, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Washington's Hill Rag (Article), 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - The Washington Hospital Center, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - The Washington Informer, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Washington National Cathedral, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Washington Performing Arts Society, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - The Washington Post, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Washington Project of Art, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - Washington Restaurant & Beverage Association, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Washington Teachers Union, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - The Washington Times, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Washington Urban League - Cooper, M, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - Washington View Magazine, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - Waterfront Washington Association, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - Way of the Cross Church, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - Webster Society, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - Whitehurst Freeway, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 36)
    - Whitman - walker Clinic, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 37)
    - Widening Horizons, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 38)
    - Wider Opportunities for Women, Inc., 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 39)
    - Wilkes, Artis, Hendrick & Lone, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 40)
    - Willing Aid Committee, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 41)
    - Wisconsin Ave Coridor Committee, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 42)
    - WJLA, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 43)
    - Women's Bar Association, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 44)
    - Women's Legal Defense Fund, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 45)
    - Word Evangelistic Ministries, Inc., 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 46)
    - World Youth Development Association, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 47)
    - WRC Talk Radio, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 48)
    - WRC - TVA, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 49)
    - WUSA, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 50)
    - WVCB, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 51)
    - Wylie Courts Forum Agenda, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 52)
    - Y.M.C.A. of Metropolitan Wash., 1986-1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 53)
    - Youth Opportunities Unlimited, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 54)
    - Zaccheus Medical Clinic, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 55)
    - Zion Baptist Church, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 56)
    - Politcal Correspondence with/concerning Institutions and Issues, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Political Correspondence with/concerning Institutions and Issues, 1979; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Politcal Correspondence with/concerning Instituions and Issues, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Politcal Correspondence with/concerning Institutions and Issues, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Politcal Correspondence with/concerning Institutions and Issues, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Issues and events, 1985-1990; Series 4 Subseries 2
    - 8 DC-Help, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Abandoned Building & Vacant Lot Farm, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Abortion, 1987-1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Abandoned Property, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Abortion Funding Restrictions, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - AIDS Issue, 1987-1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - AIDS in Prisons [1/2], 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - AIDS in Prison [2/2], 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Anacostia Park - Riverfest, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Anatomy of Street Murders UDC Book, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Black History Month, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Black National Anthem, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Boarder Baby, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Chesapeake Bay General Information, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Child Care, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Closing Alley, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Community Based Residential Facilities, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Community Based Residential Facilities (CBRFs) [1/2], 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Community Based Residential Facilities [2/2], 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Correctional Facilities, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Crack Prevention Posters & Brochures, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - CONSERN, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Correctional Facilities, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Crime Prevention Corresopondence, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Crime Strategy Meeting, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - D.C. Residency Requirement, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - D.C. Special Olympics, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - D.C. Rape Crisis Center Annual Report to the Community, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - DC State Student Incentive Grant Applications, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - D.C. Sunday Softball League, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Deaf Heritage Week Recipients, Undated; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Death Penalty, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - District Building Traffic, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Drug Actions, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Drug Enforcement Briefing 4/22/89, April 22, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Drug Enforcement Forum [1/3], 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Drug Enforcement Forum [2/3], 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Drug Enforcement Forum [3/3], 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Drug Forum, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Drug Free America, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Drugs [1/2], 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Drugs [2/2], 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Earth Day Tree Planning, 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Emergency Ambulance Services Testimony Before Fautroy, 1987; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Establishing and Maintaining a Small Business, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Events: Thanksgiving Basket Distribution, Undated; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Face the People Forum, 1985; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Farrakhan, Lewis, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Fire Prevention, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Food Assistance for Senior Citizens, 1983; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Fourth National Policy Institute, 1983; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Gasoline Vapor Nozzles, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Gays and Lesbian Democratic Auction Fundraiser, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - General [1/2], 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - General [2/2], 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Generations of Fashion, 1987; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Generic Drugs '86, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Georgia Ave Day Appreciation Dinner/Dance, 1985; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Grateful Dead Concert, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - H St. Festival Day, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Halfway House Meeting 7/16/85 St. Phillips Church, July 16, 1985; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Halfway Houses, 1985; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Health Care, 1986-1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Health Care, 1988-1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Health Insurance, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Holiday Season Support Fund, 1984-1985; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Homeless, 1985-1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Homeless, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Homeless, 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Homeless, 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Homeless, 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Homeless, 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Homeless, Undated; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Homeless [1/3], 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Homeless [2/3], Undated; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Homeless [3/3], Undated; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Homeless - Services, 1983; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Home Loan Mortgages by Five Largest Banks, 1984; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Housing, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Housing Programs, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Inauguration Day January 1, 1985, Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Incinerators [1/2], 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Incinerators [2/2], 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Insurance, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Insurance Discrimination [1/3], 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Insurance Discrimination [2/3], 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Insurance Discrimination [3/3], 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Issues on Recent Budget Deliberations, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Jail, 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Jail/Police Matters, Assault Statistics, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Jails/Prisons, 1985-1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Jail Site, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Justice for Janitors Campaign, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Labor Issues Raised by AIDS Crisis, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Lady Bird Johnson Celebration, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Laundromat, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Lesbian/Gay, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Maine Lobster Bake Fundraiser, 1984; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - March on Washington 25th Anniversary, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1986-1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Mayor's Arts Awards, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Mayor's Drug Summit, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Mental Health, 1987; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Medicaid Benefits, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Metering and Submetering of Apartments, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Metropolitan Square, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Miller Report on Black Community Leaders, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Minority Business Opportunity Commission Awards, 1987; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Minority Business Siminars, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - McKinley's Sixth Annual Debutante Cotillion, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - MLK Memorial Press Conf. March '88, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Monte Carlo Night Party, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Mount Vernon Square Property, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Multi-Door Dispute Resolution Program, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - National Black Leadership Roundtable, 1987; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - National Domestic Violence Awareness Month (October), Undated; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - National Independence Day Festival & Parade, 1987; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Nehemiah Participants, Undated; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - New Clippings 1988-1989, Drug Trafficking and Homicide, Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Newsletters, Undated; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - No Easy Answer, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - No Fault Insurance, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Non-smokers Guide to Washington, 1977; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - One Fund Drive, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Old Macmillan Reservoir, 1987; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Operation Fight Back Anti-Drug Rally, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Orioles, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Parking, 1988-1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Paul Collins Portrait of an Artist, Undated; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Polio Society Fundraiser, 1987; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Pop Branch Improvement Project, 1987; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Pro Choice March, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Professional Networking, 1987; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Promotion Propaganda, Undated; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Prostitution, 1987; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Public Health, Undated; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Public Health, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Questions, Undated; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Real Property Tax Rates, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Rent-a-teen Program, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Rent-a-teen: Stephenson, Grace, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Restrictions on South Capitol Bridge, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Riverfest, 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - School Based Clinics, 1987; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - "School Without Drugs" Book, 1987; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Seat Belt, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Sex and Your Telephone, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Shelters [1/2], 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Shelters [2/2], 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Shelters, 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - SCLC 30th Annual Convention, 1987; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Small Business Forum, 1986; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Snow Emergency Routes - Hot 51, Undated; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Supercans, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Surrogate Fatherhood, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Surrogate Parenting, 1987-1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Tax Issues [1/4], 1989-1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Tax Issues [2/4], 1989-1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Tax Issues [3/4], 1989-1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Tax Issues [4/4], 1989-1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Tax Issues [1/2], 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Tax Issues [2/2], 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Totalitarians for the Homeless, Undated; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Transportation, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Transportations Articles, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Unifest '88, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Unregistered Firearm Info, 1988; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Vacant Properties, 1985; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Virgin Islands Investigation, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Washington Afro-American Newspaper (Article & Letter to Frances Murphy), 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Washington Clean and Beautiful, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Washington is a Capital City, 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Washington Metro Drug Stats. 2/1988, Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Weapon and Assault Accessories, 1989; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Political Correspondence with/Concerning Institutions and Issues [1/2], 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Political Correspondence with/Concerning Institutions and Issues [2/2], 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Political Correspondence with/Concerning Institutions and Issues, 1990; Series 4 subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Environmental issues, 1984-1990; Series 5
  This series contains reports, correspondence, and memos related to environmental issues including among others hazardous waste, DC Soil and Water Conservation District, litter, solid waste reduction, and recycling.
  - Air Quality, 1988; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Air Quality/ Emergency Preparedness, 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Anacostia River, 1989; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Asbestos Licensing and Control Act of 1987, 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Citizens' Coalition for Recycling, 1990; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Council of Government Air Quality Planning Committee, 1982-1989; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Council of Government - Recycling [1/2], 1989; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Council of Government - Recycling [2/2], 1989; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - District of Columbia Soil and Water Conservation District, 1982-1988; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - DC Soil and Water and Conservation District, 1989; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - DC Sanctuary City Campaign, 1987; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - District of Columbia Soil and Water Conservation District, 1990; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - DC Soil and Water Conservation District, 1983-1989; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Drinking Water (Lead, etc.), 1987; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Earth Day, 1990; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Emergency Planning and Community Right to Know Act of 1986, Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Emergency Planning and Community Right to Know Act, 1988; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Policy, 1989; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - European Recycling Trip, 1988; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Frequently Asked Questions, Undated; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Hazardous Materials Liability Limitations Act of 1985, Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Hazardous Materials Study Commission, 1986; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Hazardous Material Study Commission Act of 1986 - Public Hearing, Undated; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Hazardous Materials Study Commission Act of 1986, Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Hazardous Materials Study Commission - Appointment of Gregory Talley, 1987; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Hazardous Materials Study Commission - Budget, 1988; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Hazardous Materials Study Commission - Correspondence, 1986; Series 5 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Hazardous Materials Study Commission - Marlene McKetty, 1986; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Hazardous Materials Study Commission - Members, 1986; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Hazardous Materials Transportations - Information [1/2], Undated; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Hazardous Materials Study Commission - Members, 1986; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Hazardous MAterials Study Commission - Minutes, 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Hazardous Materials Study Commission - Mark Selikson, 1988; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Hazardous Materials Study Commission - Organizational Meeting, October 17, 1986; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Hazardous Materials Study Commission - Organizational Meeting, November 7, 1986; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Hazardous Materials Study Commission/Organizational Meeting, December 12, 1986; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Hazardous Materials Study Commission - Sign In Sheets, 1986; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Hazardous Materials Study Commission - Stewart Petroleum, 1986; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Hazardous Materials Transportation Act of 1985, 1985-1988; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Hazardous Materials Transportation Act of 1985 - DC Advisory Task Force, Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Hazardous Materials Transportation - Information [2/2], Undated; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Hazardous Waste, Undated; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Hazardous Waste Amendments Act of 1984, Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Hazardous Waste Articles, 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Hunter Polo Soil Erosion, 1989; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Infectious Waste, 1988; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Litter Free DC, 1986; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Litter Free Washington Committee - Members, Undated; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Litter - Ordinances, Undated; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Litter and Solid Waste Reduction, Undated; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Litter and Solid Waste Reduction Commission Meeting, 1987; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Litter and Solid Waste Reduction Commission, 1987; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Litter and Solid Waste Reduction Commission, 1988; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - LSWRC - McLaughlin, Stephen, 1987; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - LSWRC - Poster Contest, 1988; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 5)